who the [ __ ] did he give ukraine to if we are
кто он подарил украину с хуя ли бы мы
occupiers [ __ ] good afternoon
оккупанты [__] добрый день
look I ask people from russia
смотрите я у людей из россии спрашиваю
how you feel about the war in ukraine it’s
как вы относитесь к войне в украине
ok if it doesn’t
нормально в том случае если не будет
that
то
is you support the fact that putin’s
есть вы поддерживаете вот то что путин
Hawaiian wedge is supporting this so
гавайского клин в это поддерживаете так
look here  remember the groan now, this
посмотри вот вспомни стон вот сейчас вот
is what is happening now, that is, you will
то что сейчас происходит то есть вы
support that you sent troops to ukraine
поддержите что вы ввели войска в украину
yes, well, you yourself are from which region of
да хорошо вот вы сами с какого региона
russia,
россии
just yes, but what do you have in rostov
просто да а вот что там у вас в ростове
like they say about these nationalist
типа говорят про эти националистические
battalions, this is what we have in ukraine  with
батальоны вот что у нас в украине с
these battalions that there
этими батальонами что там
often we are where the
часто мы то где
battalions serve as the
батальонах служат
occupying occupier
оккупационных оккупанта
baku baku on the tank of pandas so I understand yes in
баку баку по баку панд так я понял да в
Russians like so wait well, so what
русских типа так подождите ну так а что
happened to us that your idea q show
у нас случилось что ваша идея q понты
off the occupiers went there to
поехали туда в мариуполь
mariupol yes well, not a foreign country
оккупанты да ну а не чужую страну чужую
occupiers came to a foreign country, and
страну приехали оккупанты а
someone and who is an occupier, tell me
кто-то а кто такой оккупант вот скажите
what the word occupier
что такое слово оккупант означает
means what the word occupation means what does
что означает слово оккупация вот
occupation mean
оккупация что означает
[muses  ka]
[музыка]
mira tell me what the word
мира скажите что означает слово
occupation means occupant what does this word mean
оккупация оккупант что это слово значит
is where is ukraine nt who he
это где находится украина нт кто он
gave ukraine here what does the word occupation mean
подарил украину здесь что означает слово
i understood you don’t know what the word
я понял вы не знаете что означает слово
occupation means yes
оккупация да
you don’t know what is occupiers what
вы не знаете что такое оккупанты что
is occupation
такое оккупация
just just say that  such an occupier,
просто просто скажи что такое оккупант
and what is
да и что такое оккупация
occupation, you can formulate it in Russian
вот вы можете сформулировать русским
if you are educated people so they are
языком если вы образованные люди так они
some kind of gopniks, so what does the word occupation mean, it
какие-то гопники так что означает слово
’s already super right yes yes it’s normal
вот уже супер правильно да да нормально
that is, I see yes you are an educated person
то есть вижу да вы образованный человек
now look that is
теперь смотри то есть вы
how you are doing  someone else’s de tu
каким образом занимается чужая de tu
audit,
аудит
but if you are in some village like that,
а если же вы в каком-то селе таком
show me this hut that you behind you are
покажите мне вот эту избушку которую вас
a
сзади
[ __ ] vovka and live in poor strength and the
ёханый вовка и бедном силе живете и
dead, I understand it’s simple when I meet
мертвецов я понял простая когда встречаю
some dude and know from the poverty of
каких-то чувака и знать из бедность
downtrodden villages they will tell you everything here
забитых сел они все расскажу что тут
nato bombed a
нато бомбили
kiss show me just show me
поцелуй покажите вот просто покажите мне
this house show me your dead man or is
хату эту домик покажите ваш убитый или
he cool you tell me about
он классный вы мне расскажете про
you can’t make a normal door to the house in Ukraine, you
украину в это себе дом не можете
already saw the
нормальной двери в дом сделать аж видел
whales the windows were killed,
китам окна убиты
they know show show at home this is how
они знают покажите покажите дома вот как
he looks like he was killed and
он выглядит он убитый и
don’t just keep the supplies I didn’t have time to
не держите просто поставки я не успел
see you turned
посмотреть вы так провернули
it like that show the door how the door was given how the
покажите дверь вот как дверь выдали как
entrance
вход
show show  show the door,
покажи покажите покажите дверь
I just see that you live in
я просто смотрю что вот вы живете в
some such poor conditions more
каких-то таких бедных условиях
than once, you can, let's show,
не раз к можете давайте покажите
let's
давайте
see, I'm from
смотрите смотрите я из америки
America, from America
есть у из америки
, the state of New York,
штат нью-йорк
where will you get to, these will help us, you
куда вы дойдете эти поможете нам вы из
won't leave your village, okay who  it’s
своего села не выйдете ладно кто-то
suitable, you’ve even been there in Moscow, you
подойдет вызван вы даже там в москве не
’ve never really been, but
были никогда правда не были а
[music
[музыка]
] look where you
вот смотри где вы дальше ростовской
cut yours beyond the Rostov region, where you
области своим вырезали вот куда вы
went further in Europe, were at least once
дальше выезжали в европе были хоть раз
why that’s what you don’t like the Germans, no, you
почему вот что вы германцам не любите
know what the imperious  forget them
нет вот властное знаете чем забыть их
such Russian clubs of legs tamber
таких российские клубы ног тэмбер шиваны
shivana petr and we are there just ukrainian protein
петр и мы там просто украины протеина
there about you there europe from your guilt this is a
там про ты там европы от вины свой это
size and then glory is not forgotten
ростовка и потом забыто славе никуда не
anywhere  a cool man
простой мужик
against the background of such a way of life from attacks on pancakes
на фоне такую быту их от атак на блинных
and the Internet on a Pindos
и интернет на пиндосов скому телефоне
phone and a European man of a
так и европейского человека малины
Russian raspberry even here’s a story like we have
российского even вот рассказу як у нас
a nasty thing we have on such so on and so
там поганое у нас на такие так далее так
Russia so rennar beef peter would they
россия так реннара биф питера бы они
live in her side  and
живут в бок ней и
ready peter him something and created you and
готове петр ему-то и создал тебя и и
tiles and rendered food in classic [ __ ] morons
плитку и оказал food in classic [__]